

# **QUYEN VUONG**

## • DETAILS •

Kanagawa Prefecture Japan +81 90 1693 9896 jvvincewang@gmail.com

> Date / Place of birth 1992 Vietnam

> > ° SKILLS °

C#

Java

C++

Shell

Cocos2d-x

Unity

MySQL

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Git

Python

AWS

Agile Scrum

Microsoft Azure

PlayFab

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese

English

Japanese

Chinese

Cantonese

HOBBIES

#### PROFILE

I am a software developer from Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam. Worked as an ERP system architect for 2 years after I graduated and moved to Japan to start my game development career from Jan 2015 until now. With 7 years of developing game experience as a full-stack engineer (used to work as server engineer for about 3 years, my main field is client).

My experiences span across genres, from simulation games to Match 3, turn-based card games, idle games, and currently block chain games, which are completely new to me, as well as a broad range of disciplines including network, API, Editor tools, gameplay, generic system, AI, UI programming,... I consider myself a combination of passionate and disciplined. I love pushing my limits by learning new techniques and technologies.

Besides engineering experience, I'm also working as Unity team project sub-leader, responding on adjusting development schedule, mentor for new members, fresher... dealing with other team leaders to make project development process go smooth and in time.

After years of working in the game industry, I decided to take on new challenges. Instead of creating solutions for some specific problems in some specific games, I'm thinking of creating new things to solve more problems from a wider perspective.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## VR Game Developer at Thirdverse.inc, Tokyo, Japan

June 2022 — Present

- Implement Game-play logic and game battle system.
- · Research and implement shader and VFX for battle scenes and environment
- Worked as a bridge engineer, designing, and implementing back-end game systems, translating and managing the communication between the Japan team and the US team.

Platform: Meta Quest 2, Pico, PSVR2

# Technologies:

- Unity: Addressable, VContainer, Shader Graph, Final IK, A\* Path Finding,...
- UE4 C++, UE4 Blueprint.

# Unity Game Development Team Lead at Wanaka Tech Ltd, Japan

May 2021

- Research, design, and implement game core system, tools to speed up the development process.
- Decide technologies to use inside our production. Take part in the development process and review code with the team.
- Management team schedule.
- · Scrum master.

Platform: PC Standalone, MacOS Standalone, iOS, Android

#### Technologies:

• Unity: Addressable, VContainer, Shader Graph, Final IK, A\* Path Finding,...

- Coding, Streaming Coding,...
  - Play Guitar, MOBA games, Basketball
  - Watch anime, manga...

## · LINKS ·

**Linkedin** 

#### PSM2 Certificate Confirm

#### Client Engineer at 10ANTZ Co.Ltd, Japan

June 2019 — Present

- Design and develop the game core system, unity editor tool to speed up the development process.
- Implement game features and improve the existed game system.
- R&D team, focus on research and create XR application prototype

#### Unity Game App Development Team at MIRABO JSC, Japan

January 2019

- Developing XR games, applications for Japan clients.
- Working directly with our clients to propose solutions for their problems.
- Research and implement new technology to resolve our client problems.
- · Bridge System Engineer.
- Mentor for members at any level, skill up and support members to resolve problems.

# System Engineer - BrSE - Technical Support at Pocket Queries Co.Ltd, Japan

June 2018 — April 2019

- Focus on developing training simulation applications in VR environment.
- Take part in working support system development on MR environment.
- Working with Openpose AI lib to capture real animation bone and parse it into Unity 3D model.
- Focus on improving development process management.
- Management Vietnam team schedule.
- · Work as bridge system engineer between Vietnam side and Japan side
- Work as a technical consultant, working directly with clients to propose solutions to their problems.

#### System Engineer - Team Sub Leader at GREST Co.Ltd - CyberAgent, Japan

January 2015 — May 2018

- Focus on implementing game features and improving development process management on new game projects.
- Conducted research Unity asset to implement into our project.
- Participated in code review processes and formulated designing standards.
- Designed and developed the game core system.
- Designed and developed Unity Editor tool to speed up development time and operation process.
- Implemented game event, maintained game server.
- Migrated game chatting's database from MongoDB to PostgreSQL.
- Participated in new game prototype development on Cocos2d-x.
- Manager team schedule, break down task list, discuss and adjust development timetable.

#### Programmer at FUJINET SYSTEM JSC, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

July 2014 — December 2014

• Implement MS Reporting Service into product.

### Programmer at Chingluh Viet Nam, Viet Nam

May 2013 — June 2014

- Translated document and communication between Vietnamese develop team and Chinese customer.
- Team schedule management, maintained, designed, and developed features based on the requirement

#### EDUCATION

1

Bachelor's Degree In Software Development, Saigon Technology University, Viet Nam November 2010 — April 2013

# Certificate of Developing Program with C#, University Of Science Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

May 2013 — July 2013

## Certificate of JLPT N2 level, Self Study, Tokyo, Japan

August 2018 — July 2018

# PSM2, Self Study

Self-study PSM base on experience from the workplace. And take certificate after year of applied scrum in development.

# Technical detail

- Unity
  - Asset management: Addressable, Unity Legacy AssetBundle
  - Game-play package: A\* Path Finding, Unity Navmesh Agent, Odin Serializer, Final IK, Shader graph, VContainer (DI plugin), Cinemacine, Unity Native Plugin, Unity XR interaction toolkit, some haptic plugin, Unity Input System, Netcode for gameobject, TextMesh Pro, DOTween, Enhanced Scroller....
  - System: Job System, UniTask.
  - Tracking, and analysis: Unity IAP, Firebase Remote Configuration.
  - Networking: Photon PUN, Photon Fusion, Message Pack, MagicOnion, PlayFab system.
  - CI/CD: Jenkins, Gitlab runner, Github action, Python, Fastlane.
- UE4,5
  - UE C++, UE Blueprint.
- · Back-end
  - AWS cloud services. Azure Function, PlayFab